So it seems like this lnternet thing is here to stay,huh?
看来网际网路是不会消失了
It's okay not to talk.
不说话也没关系
Hey,you guys,guess what.
你们猜怎样？
-Barry and Mindy are getting a divorce. -Oh,my God.
-贝瑞和明蒂要离婚了 -天哪
What is the matter with you?
你是怎么搞的？
No. Barry and Mindy.
不，是贝瑞和明蒂
Oh,sorry. I hear "divorce," I immediately go to Ross.
对不起 我一听到离婚就觉得是罗斯
Who's Barry and Mindy?
谁是贝瑞和明蒂？
Barry was the guy that I almost married, and Mindy was my best friend.
贝瑞是我差点要嫁的人 明蒂是我最要好的朋友
Wasn't he cheating on you with her?
他们不是有一腿？
But that just means he was falling asleep on top of her instead of me.
对，但那只表示他做到一半 会在她身上睡着
-Why did they get divorced? -Well,apparently...
-他们为什么要离婚？ -显然是...
she caught him cheating on her with someone else.
他外遇被她逮到
Isn't that sad?
很悲哀吧？
Can you imagine if I'd married him? How different would my life be?
要是我真的嫁给他 我的人生会多么不同
I've always wondered how different my life would be...
我懂你的意思，我总是在想
if I'd never gotten divorced.
要是我没有离婚会怎样
-Which time? -The first time!
哪一次？ 第一次啦
Imagine if Carol hadn't realized she was a lesbian.
真的，要是卡萝没发现 她是同性恋
I can't. I keep seeing it the good way.
我无法想像 我老是往好的方面去想
I bet I'd still be doing my karate.
那我一定还在练控手道 （空手道）
Towards the end of our marriage, I did a lot of karate to release the tension...
后来我经常练控手道
from not doing anything else physical.
好发泄缺乏肉体运动的精力
Maybe the problem was you were pronouncing it "ka-ra-tay."
也许你不念成控手道就没事了
What if I was still fat?
如果我还是很胖呢？
You wouldn't be dating me, that's for sure.
你一定不会跟我交往
-Sure I would. -Come on.
当然会 少来了
You guys really think I'm that shallow?
你们真的觉得我那么肤浅？
No,I just think Monica was that fat.
不，我只是觉得摩妮卡太胖
Hey,imagine if I'd never got fired off Days of Our Lives.
要是我没被 “我们的岁月”开除呢？
Hey. Hey,there's Carol again.
卡萝又出现了
What if I had had the guts to quit my job?
要是我有勇气辞职呢？
I'd probably be writing for The New Yorker, being paid to be funny.
我可能在帮“纽约客”写稿 拿钱搞笑
But my job's fun too. I mean,tomorrow...
现在的工作也很有趣 明天...
I don't have to wear a tie.
我不必打领带
What if I'd taken that job at Merrill Lynch?
要是我去美林证券上班呢？
-What? -Merrill Lynch?
什么？ 美林证券？
I had a massage client who worked there, and he said I had a knack for stocks.
对，我有个客人在那里上班 他说我有炒股票的头脑
Why didn't you take the job?
那你怎么不去？
Because at that time,I thought that everything that rhymed was true.
因为当时我很相信押韵这回事
I thought if I worked with stocks...
我觉得要是我去做股票
I'd have to live in a box and only eat lox and have a pet fox.
就得住地窖 只能吃安眠药，养三脚猫
Yeah,you don't want that in a broker.
这种股票经纪人的确不优
Do you guys think if all those things happened, we'd still hang out?
你们觉得如果有这些事 我们还会在一起吗？
The One That Could Have Been
本集播出：“虚拟六人行”
rainystar压制iPod-MP4
Oh,my God. Rachel Green?
天哪，瑞秋葛林？
Rob Tilman!
劳勃提尔曼
No, no, it's me. Ross.
不对，是我，罗斯
Oh,I'm sorry. Ross Tilman.
对不起，罗斯提尔曼
-No. No,no. Ross Geller. -Of course! Monica's brother.
-不是，是罗斯盖勒 -对哦，摩妮卡的哥哥
-Yeah. Right. -Wow! How are you?
没错 你好吗？
Good. Good. I'm married.
很好，我结婚了
Me too!
我也是
-Isn't it the best? -Oh,it's the best.
结婚真好不是吗？ 就是啊
-So how's Monica? -Really,really great.
摩妮卡好吗？ 非常好
Actually,she's right down the street. You should stop by and say hi.
事实上她就在前面 你应该过去打个招呼
-I would love to. -She'd be so excited.
好啊 她会很高兴
-Okay. -Come on.
好 走吧
Wait,don't you have to pay for...
等等，你不是要买…
Busty Ladies?
“巨乳女O”？
No,that's okay. Some kid asked me to pick it up for him, but I....
没关系，有个小孩托我帮他买 走吧
Don't you have to give him his money back?
你不是应该把钱还给他？
Here you go,buddy. Sorry,no porn for you.
拿去吧，抱歉，你不能看A书
Okay,let's go see Monica.
我们去找摩妮卡吧
So,Monica. Still going out with Dr. Boring,huh?
摩妮卡 你还在跟无聊医生交往？
He's not boring. He's just...
他才不无聊，他只是…
He's low-key.
只是比较低调
-Here you go, one hazelnut latte. -Thank you.
你的榛果拿铁 谢谢
You know, the hazelnut, actually not a nut.
其实榛果不是果实
It's a seed.
而是种子
Wow.
Can anyone else name a well-known seed that's been masquerading as a nut?
还有谁能说出一种 假装是果实的常见种子？
Oh,dear God. Let me think.
天哪，我想想看
What's the matter?
你怎么了？
I got another rejection letter.
我又被退稿了
They said my writing was funny, just not "Archie Comic" funny.
他们说我的东西很有趣 只是不符合“阿奇漫画”风
I gotta get back to the hospital.
亲爱的，我得回医院了
-Bye. -Bye-bye.
再见
By the way, the answer is: the Brazil nut.
对了，答案是巴西果
Was his question, "What's more boring than him?"
他的问题比他的人更无趣
And nice sweater vest, by the way.
好帅的毛线背心啊
-Stop it,guys. He's sweet. -Yeah,yeah.
你们别这样，他人很好 是啊
Hey,man. Sorry about the Archie thing.
老兄，退稿的事真可惜
You need me to give you some money?
你要我给你一些钱吗？
I may have no money, but I still have my pride.
我穷归穷，还是有骨气
Really?
是吗？
Joey doesn't have to give you the money.
也许乔伊不必给你钱
-TV stars have assistants,right? -That's an idea.
-电视明星都有助理对吧？-可行喔
If I hire an assistant, would you take money from her?
要是我请助理转交 你会收吗？
No,Joey. Chandler could be your assistant.
不是啦，钱德可以当你的助理
He could answer all your fan mail and stuff.
他可以帮你回信给影迷
-That would be great! Let's do that! -I could use the money.
-太好了，好主意，就这么办吧 -我有钱领
I'd have time to write.
还有时间写作
-Great. Welcome aboard! -Okay!
漂亮，欢迎加入 感谢
All right. Now,I need to use the bathroom.
我现在要去上厕所
Since I don't need any assistance in there,take a break!
我上厕所不用人帮 你就休息吧
All right.
好
-Hey. -Hey,Phoebe.
菲比，
Guess what. Joey just hired Chandler to be his assistant.
你猜怎样？乔伊找钱德当他的助理
That's so sweet.
真好
Oh! Hang on!
等一下
Hang on!
等我一下
Go!
说
No. No,no. I said sell when it hits 50!
不对，不对 我是说一到50点就卖
Five-oh! It's a number! It comes after four-nine!
50是一个数字，在49后面
No,it's okay. It's okay. You're allowed one mistake.
没关系，一次错误可以接受
Just kidding. You are,of course,fired.
开玩笑的，你当然被开除了
Oh,what a shame. I really liked her.
真可惜，我很喜欢她
Hey,Mon? Mon,look who I ran into!
摩妮卡，你看我遇见谁
Oh,my God,Rachel!
天哪，瑞秋
-God,you look terrific! -So do you!
-你好漂亮 -你也是
-Did you lose weight? -You are so sweet to notice.
-你是不是瘦了？-你居然注意到了
Yes,I lost 3.5 pounds!
没错，我瘦了3.5磅
You remember my friend Chandler.
记得我的朋友钱德吧
-And that's Phoebe over there. -Hi.
那位是菲比
Sit down. How long has it been since we've seen each other?
天哪，快坐下 我们多久没见面了？
1987,the day after Christmas. Sean McMahan's party.
1987年，圣诞节第二天 西恩麦克曼的派对
I played you one of my songs,you know, "lnterplanetary Courtship Ritual."
我弹了我的创作曲给你听 “星际求爱仪式”
Oh,yeah. Right.
喔对
-So,now,do you still do music? -Well,sometimes.
-你还在玩音乐吗？ -偶尔
-Come over sometime. I'll play you.. -Oh,my God!
你应该来我家，我弹… 天哪
Joey Tribbiani from Days of Our Lives just walked in here!
“我们的岁月”的 乔伊崔比亚尼刚刚走进来
-Rach,he's a friend of ours. -You're friends with Dr. Drake Ramoray?
-瑞秋，他是我们的朋友 -你们是拉莫瑞医生的朋友？
It's hard to be friends with Drake...
要跟他交朋友有点难
because of his busy schedule and the fact that he's not real.
因为他很忙，又是个虚构人物
Hey,or I could bring my keyboard here sometime.
我也可以把键盘带来
-He's coming over. -Joey?
他过来了 乔伊
I know. Here,here.
好啦，拿去
No. This is my friend Rachel. We went to high school together.
不是啦，这是我朋友瑞秋 我们是高中同学
-Hi. -Hi.
I love you on that show.
我好喜欢你演的戏
I watch you every day.
我每天都看
When you took out your own kidney to save your ex-wife...
你还捐肾救你的前妻…
even though she tried to kill you...
明明知道她想杀你
It's always nice to meet fans.
遇见影迷总是很开心
-She's not crazy,is she? -No.
她不会很神经吧？ 不会
So how you doing?
所以…你好吗？
Hang on.
等等…
Hang on. Hang on.
等等，等一下
Go!
说
Who's this?
谁？
You're gonna like working for me.
好，你要替我工作
What's your name? What kind of name is "Brindy"?
你叫什么名字？ 布伦蒂是什么鸟名字？
Stop talking.
闭嘴
All right, from now on your name is Joan.
好，以后你就叫琼安
You can pick your own last name.
姓你自己选
I can't find my pen. Did you eat that too?
我找不到我的笔 也被你吃掉了吗？
-There you are. -Uh-oh,it's my boss.
你在这里 是老板大人
Here's a list of things for you to do today.
这是你今天的工作项目
This is gonna be so great. Thank you so much.
太好了，谢谢你
I gotta go to work. I'm delivering twins today, but only one of them is mine.
我要去接生双胞胎了 但只有一个是我的骨肉
"Drop off my dry cleaning. Pick up my vitamins."
把衣服送去干洗 去拿我的维他命
"Teach me how to spell vitamins."
教我怎么写维他命
"Wear in my new jeans."
把我的新牛仔裤穿软
-You realize what you are,don't you? -What?
你知道你的角色吧？什么角色？
You're his bitch!
你是他的喽罗
No,no! No!
不！不
Wait! You didn't sit on my Kit Kats did you?
你不是压坏了我的巧克力酥吧
No,there was a little, little dip in the market...
不是，市场出了点变化
and I lost 13 million dollars.
我损失了1千3百万
But the Kit Kats are all right?
不过巧克力酥没事吧？
What am I gonna do? I can't call my office, they'll kill me.
怎么办？怎么办？ 通知公司我会被砍死
I can't call my clients, they'll kill themselves!
通知客户他们会砍自己
-Great,now my chest hurts. -What?
帅啊，现在又胸口痛 什么？
My chest hurts.
我的胸口在痛
-And now I can't breathe. -Are you having a heart attack?
现在是喘不过气来 菲比，你是心脏病发作吗？
If I were, would I have shooting pains up and down my left arm?
如果是，左臂会来回抽痛吗？
-Yes. -Then,yes. That is what I'm having.
会 那就是了
Oh,my God!
我的天哪
Okay,this thing is useless. So will you dial 911 for me?
我的手动不了了 帮我叫救护车好吗？
Come on,Phoebe, it's not that bad.
别这样，没那么严重
Most people would be excited if they didn't work for a couple weeks.
一般人如果可以休息两星期 会放鞭炮庆祝
Most people don't like their jobs. I love my job.
一般人不喜欢他们的工作 我喜欢我的工作
I've been not working for three hours, and I'm already going crazy.
我才休息3小时就快疯掉了
I miss Joan.
我想念琼安
Honey, having a heart attack is nature's way of telling you to slow down.
心脏病发就表示你该放慢脚步
I always thought having a heart attack was nature's way of telling you to die.
我一直以为心脏病发 就表示你要死了
You're not gonna die.
但是你不会死
I mean,you are going to die, but you're not gonna die today.
你迟早会死，但不是今天
I wish I was dead.
我去死算了
Let's take a walk.
我们去走走
You should consider writing for Talking Out of Your Ass magazine.
你应该考虑去替 “讲话不经大脑”杂志写稿
What's going on with you?
你最近怎么样？
Well,I've been doing a lot more of my karate.
我练控手道练得更勤了
-Still a dry spell with Carol? -Yeah.
跟卡萝还在干枯期？ 对
How long has it been since you've had sex?
你们多久没上床了？
-Well,last weekend... -Oh,that's not so bad.
到上个周末… 那还好嘛
will be two months...
就已经2个月…
since I stopped trying.
放弃尝试了
You need to spice things up.
也许你应该玩一点刺激的
-What do you mean? -I don't know.
怎么说？不晓得
You could tie her up. You could eat stuff off each other.
你们可以绑住对方 可以在对方身上吃东西
Dirty talk, menage a trois, toys.
淫言秽语，3P，辅助工具
Role-playing. You're the warden, she's the prisoner.
角色扮演 你当典狱长她当囚犯
-You're the pirate, she's the wench. -Okay,I think I got it.
你当海盗她当村姑 好，我懂了
Or you could be two stockbrokers, and you're rolling naked on the trading floor...
或者你们都当股票经纪人 在号子的地板上翻滚...
and everybody's watching.
给大家看
It never happened.
我没干过
Sorry.
抱歉
-So how is it going with Joey? -Just great. He beeps me now with codes.
你帮乔伊工作得怎样？ 很好，他现在都用暗号呼叫我
One is: "Bring me food."
1是“带吃的来”
Two is: "I'm with a girl. Bring us food."
2是“有女伴，带吃的来”
Three is: "I'm lost and I can't find food."
3是“迷路，找不到吃的”
Oh,sweetie.
辛苦你了
Is there any food around here?
这附近有吃的吗？
-Is she gonna be all right? -Yeah,she's in there.
她不会有事吧？ 对，她在里面
Oh,great.
那就好
Go take off those pants. They look ready.
脱裤子吧，看起来够软了
And over there is Brady's Pub...
那里是布瑞帝酒吧
where I like to unwind after a long day of "surgeoning."
我行完医喜欢去轻松一下
This is so amazing. What else?
好棒喔，还有呢？
Well,that is a large piece of television equipment.
那是一个大型电视台设备
And that is an old man.
那是一个老男人
-Hey,old man! -Hey.
老男人你好
Alrighty. What do you say we head back to my place?
我们要不要回我家去？
You know,I would really love to, but I shouldn't.
我很想去，但是不行
Why? Why can't the world stop turning...
为什么？ 为什么世界不能停止转动
just for a moment, just for us?
只要一下下，只为了我们？
Isn't that a line from the show?
那不是戏里的台词吗？
Yeah,but...
对，不过
I may have said those things before, but...
我或许说过同样的话，但是…
I never truly meant them until now.
只有这一刻 我才是真心的
That's a line from the show too!
那也是戏里的台词
Okay,you watch too much TV.
你看太多电视了
Here's the freshly squeezed orange juice you asked for.
乔伊，现榨的柳橙汁来了
Thanks.
谢谢
There's pulp in that.
里面有果肉
怎样？
I thought we talked about this. I don't like pulp.
我们不是讲过了 我不喜欢果肉
No pulp. Pulp isn't juice. All juice.
不要果肉 果肉不是果汁，我要纯果汁
I'm sorry. I guess I just like the pulp.
对不起，我就是喜欢果肉
I'm sorry. I am being so rude.
天哪，抱歉，我太不客气了
Rachel,would you like a soda or something?
瑞秋，你要喝汽水什么的吗？
Because Chandler will run right out and get it.
钱德会马上去帮你买
Yeah, well, sure, iced tea would be great.
好啊，就冰红茶吧
Iced tea.
冰红茶
Okay. Anything for you,sir?
好，那您要什么？
Did I not just tell him?
我刚才不是说了吗？
Okay, look, Chandler, if this is gonna work...
钱德，你想替我工作
you have got to listen.
就要专心听我说话
You're gonna throw that juice at me, aren't you?
你要拿果汁泼我对不对？
It's not all juice.
这不是纯果汁
So,honey,this morning was fun,huh?
亲爱的，早上很有意思吧？
Me hopping in on you in the shower there?
我在淋浴间扑向你
Yeah, maybe someday we could get a place with two bathrooms.
是啊，也许以后可以换一栋 有两间浴室的房子
Look,Carol,I was thinking maybe...
卡萝，我在想
Maybe we can spice things up a little.
或许我们可以玩一点刺激的
-What do you mean? -Carol,our sex life. It's just not..
怎么说？卡萝，我们的性生活不美…
-Dad! -Hey there,little fella!
爸 小鬼头
Why don't we get some shoes on you,huh?
你要不要去穿鞋？
Why don't you show Dad how you can put your shoes on in your room.
自己去房里穿鞋给爸爸看
Seriously,our sex life.
说真的，我们的性生活…
I was thinking maybe,I don't know...
我想说或许…
we could try some new things,you know,for fun.
我们可以换个新花样玩玩
-Like what? -Well,I don't know.
像什么？ 我不知道
What if we were to...
互相把对方...
tie each other up?
绑起来如何？
Some people eat stuff off one another.
有些人会在对方身上吃东西
Yeah.
不好
You know,we could try dirty talk.
我们可以说脏话助长情趣
-We could have a threesome. -I love that idea!
-我们可以玩3P -这个我喜欢
Who sold a story to Archie Comics?
谁的故事 被“阿奇漫画”采用了？
Oh, my God, that's so great.
天哪，太棒了
You're a published writer. I wish I had a present for you.
你有著作了，真想送你贺礼
Wait a minute.
等等
My last Kit Kat bar.
我的最后一个巧克力酥
-You want to share it? -Okay!
要不要跟我分？ 好啊
Chandler,I know you're mad. I'm sorry.
钱德，我知道你很生气 我想跟你道歉
I was a total jerk. Completely over the line.
我太混蛋、太超过了
I just... I hate pulp.
但我就是讨厌果肉
You know how Monica feels about low-fat mayonnaise?
就像摩妮卡 对低脂美乃滋的感觉
It's not mayonnaise!
那不是美乃滋
Anyway,I just wanted to say I'm sorry,and here.
总之我只想说对不起 这个给你
-What's this? -Fresh-squeezed orange juice,with pulp.
什么东西？现榨的柳橙汁
-Just the way you like it. -Thanks,man.
有你喜欢的果肉 谢了
Hey,Joey.
乔伊
Joey? Chandler sold a story to Archie Comics.
乔伊，钱德的故事 被“阿奇漫画”采用了
That's great! Congratulations! What's the story?
天哪，太棒了，恭喜 是什么故事？
You wouldn't care. It's just a stupid comic book story.
也没什么 只是个白痴的漫画故事
Are you kidding me? I love Archie and the whole gang.
开什么玩笑 我最爱阿奇那票人了
Well,Archie needs money to fix his jalopy.
阿奇需要钱修他的老爷车
But he doesn't want Reggie to just give him the money.
但他不想跟瑞吉拿钱
So Reggie hires him as his assist..
所以瑞吉就找他当助…
As his butler.
当管家
And then makes him do crazy things...
然后叫他做一堆无聊事
Like bring him milk shakes that can't have lumps in them.
例如叫他买不能有结块的奶昔
Wait a minute. That sounds a little familiar.
等等，有点耳熟喔
Did they already do that one? I think I read it!
这个故事画过了吧 我觉得我看过
Monica,listen. I have to ask.
摩妮卡，我一定要问
Okay,Joey Tribbiani invited me back to his apartment.
乔伊崔比亚尼找我去他家
-Does he do this with a lot of girls? -Yeah,a lot. A lot,a lot.
他经常找女人去他家吗？ 对，经常，经常的经常
And I'm one of them.
而我是其中之一
I just cannot believe this. I mean,Joey Tribbiani.
我真不敢相信 乔伊崔比亚尼耶
You don't have to use his last name.
你不必一直叫他的姓
But, Monica, come on, it's Joey Tribbiani.
但是他是乔伊崔比亚尼
I guess you have to.
看来你是非叫不可
It's none of my business, but aren't you married?
虽然与我无关 但你不是结婚了？
Yeah.
对啊
I wish we could just not be married for a little bit.
真希望我们能不结婚一下
You know,I just wish we could be, like,on a break.
真希望我们能分开一下
Well,you're not.
你们没有
It's easy for you. You're not married. You can have sex with whoever you want.
你当然轻松，你又没结婚 爱跟谁上床就跟谁上床
Yeah,I can.
没错
Don't think I don't. I do.
别以为我没有
I mean,all the time. You bet!
我一天到晚都有
Monica?
摩妮卡
You've done it,right?
你有经验了吧？
Of course I have. What do you think, I'm,like,some 30-year-old virgin?
当然有 你以为我是30岁的老处女吗
Oh,my God. You're a 30-year-old virgin.
天哪，你是30岁的老处女
Say it louder. The guy in the back didn't hear you.
再大声一点 后面那个人应该没听到
Yeah,I heard it.
我听到了
It's not like I haven't had the opportunity.
我不是没有机会
I'm just waiting for the perfect guy.
我只是在等完美的对象
I'm seeing this guy Roger. He's not perfect...
我正在跟罗杰交往 他并不完美...
but I'm thinking maybe I should get it over with.
但是 或许我应该将就一下
You know,give him my flower.
把我的花芯给他
Oh,my God,do it! Honey, you've waited long enough.
天哪，那就给吧 你等得够久了
-You know what? You are right. -Sex doesn't have to be a big deal.
你知道吗？你说得对 没错，没必要看得那么严重
There shouldn't be all these rules and restrictions.
性爱不该有任何规则和限制
People should be able to sleep with whoever they want, whenever..
人应该随时随地，想跟谁上…
Rachel,I'm never gonna think it's okay for you to cheat on your husband.
瑞秋，我觉得你不该背叛老公
What do you know,virgin?
你懂什么，处女
Phoebe?
菲比
Why is smoke coming out of the bathroom?
厕所怎么有烟冒出来？
The doctor said that could be one of the side effects.
医生说可能会有这种副作用
Put the cigarette out.
菲比，把烟熄掉
No,it's not a cigarette. The smoke is coming out of me!
不，那不是香烟 烟是从我身上冒出来的
-Put it out. -Okay,okay!
熄掉 好啦好啦
-I'm so glad you're here. -Come on.
真高兴有你们在 躺好
-I got it. -Give it to me!
我来接 给我
-I got it. -Give it!
Hello?
喂？
She can't come to the phone now.
她现在不方便接电话
Right. No problem. Okay, bye-bye.
好，没问题，再见
Was it my work? Were they mad? Was it Jack? Did he yell?
是公司吗？他们生气吗？ 是杰克吗？他有大小声吗？
No,just relax. Nobody yelled.
别紧张，没有人大小声
Jack was making sure you were getting better.
杰克只是打来问你有没有好转
Thank God.
谢天谢地
Yeah, she's fired.
她被开除了
You've done all you can, Dr. Wesley.
你已经尽力了
You've got to let her go.
该放手了
Goodbye and Godspeed, Hope Brady.
别了，好好安息吧
Not so fast, Wesley.
且慢，卫斯理
Ramoray!
拉莫瑞
That's right,Wesley.
没错，卫斯理
I just stopped by to say that you're not a real doctor.
我只是来说 你是个冒牌医生
And that woman's brain is fine.
那个女人的脑部好得很
Oh,thank God.
太好了
-Hope? Hope? -Drake.
霍普，霍普 是你
You're not dying,Hope.
霍普，你不会死
You're gonna live a long, healthy life. With me.
你会跟我过着幸福快乐的日子
Oh,Drake.
Okay.
好
Here we go.
我决定了
好
Hi,Joey? It's Rachel.
乔伊，我是瑞秋
I am free tomorrow night.
我明天晚上有空
Yeah,sure,sure, I can bring some sandwiches.
没问题，我可以带三明治去
So,honey...
亲爱的
this threesome thing?
关于玩3P的事
How are we even gonna start to find..?
你要去哪里找…
Actually, I'm making a list of women I know who might be into this.
我把可能有兴趣的女人 列了出来
Boy.
天哪
Someone's been doing their homework.
有人很用功喔
I know Gail Rosten is in there twice...
是啊 我知道我列了两次盖儿罗斯坦
but she is so....
但是她好…
Oh,I know.
我知道
You know, just talking about it is getting me kind of...
光是用讲的就让我有点…
I know. Me too.
我也是
I think Ben's asleep.
是吗？班已经睡了
You know,I think it'll be better if we just save it.
我觉得我们最好储存精力
也对
Right. Save it. I can do that.
储存精力，没问题
Why do you always wear that dumb hat?
你为什么老是戴着那顶帽子？
What,you late for your paper route?
送报要迟到了吗？
"Hi,Mr. and Mrs. Jones. Here's your paper.
“琼斯先生太太，报纸来了”
I'm sorry about your window."
“抱歉砸破你们的窗户”
Hey,Phoebe.
菲比
How's it going?
还好吗？
I've got to get out of this bed. I'm going crazy here! Crazy!
我得离开这张床，我快疯掉了
Here you go,sweetie.
喝吧
What the hell is this, herbal tea? I hate herbal tea.
这是花草茶？我讨厌花草茶
Well,I put some honey in it.
但是我加了蜂蜜
-She doesn't know she was fired? -No,the doctors say it may kill her.
她还不知道她被开除了对吧？ 对，医生说她会没命
What are you girls whispering about over there?
你们两个女生在窃窃私语什么
But I think we should tell her.
不过我觉得应该告诉她
Look, Phoebe, maybe this whole heart-attack thing is a sign...
菲比，也许心脏病发是个徵兆
that you should start thinking about getting a different job.
提醒你该考虑转行了
Okay, what is this, a stupid contest?
现在是在比赛谁笨吗？
Because we've got a winner here.
优胜者已经揭晓了
He's right. People are not supposed to have heart attacks at 31.
菲比，他说得对 31岁不应该有心脏病
I know. But if I didn't work there, what else would I do?
我知道，但是不做股票 我还能做什么？
-You used to like playing the guitar. -That was lucrative. Smart like your brother.
你以前喜欢弹吉他 真有吸引力啊 跟你哥一样聪明
What about the massage thing? That never gave you a heart attack.
那按摩呢？ 按摩可没让你生过病
Pulling in a salary in the high six figures...
拿六位数的薪水
or rubbing gross naked people for chump change.
还是帮恶心的裸男裸女按摩赚小钱
What do I do? What will I do?
我该怎么选择？
I mean,it's just so realistic.
它好逼真喔
I know.
就是啊
His name's Pat.
他的名字叫拍拍
Pat the dog.
拍拍狗
I get it!
我懂了
Ready for a refill?
你…要续杯了吗？
I probably shouldn't.
我不该再喝了…
So I will!
所以我要喝
-It's like it's raining. -Pretty cool,huh?
感觉好像下雨喔 很酷吧？
But if you think you could put a fish in there...
要是你以为把鱼扔进去
and it wouldn't get sucked into the mechanism, you'd be wrong.
不会卡进机器里，那你就错了
Can I use your bathroom?
可以借用洗手间吗？
It's right through there.
就在那里面
You know,I gotta tell you.
你知道么
If someone told me a week ago...
要是一个星期前有人对我说
that I would be peeing in Joey Tribbiani's apartment...
我会在乔伊崔比亚尼家撒尿…
Life's pretty great,isn't it?
人生真美好对吧？
I hope you're hungry.
希望你饿了
We're starting with oysters.
我们先吃生蚝
You know what they say about oysters, don't you?
你知道生蚝的作用吧？
They have parasites?
它有寄生虫？
不是
Some people say that oysters are an aphrodisiac.
有人说生蚝是一种春药
-What people? -People.
什么人说的？ 就是人嘛
People say it.
有人说的
Come here.
过来
So,oysters,huh?
生蚝是吧？
Then we'll have a little Middle Eastern couscous.
然后再吃一些中东的库司库司
Something we can eat...
我们可以...
with our hands.
用手拿着吃
When we were studying communicable diseases..
有意思，我们学到传染病时…
No,no. No.
不是
It's sensual.
这样才性感
Didn't know. Okay.
我都不知道，好 好
讨厌
Sorry,it's the hospital.
抱歉，医院找我
The food looks great. Save me some?
菜都很棒，帮我留一点？
I can't promise anything.
我可不敢保证
We're really gonna do this?
我们是来真的对吧？
Looks like it.
看样子是
If this is too weird for you, you can still back out anytime..
要是你觉得很怪 我们还是可以随时喊…
I got it!
我来开 好
苏珊
-Thank you so much for coming. -I wouldn't have missed it for the world.
谢谢你的加入 我怎么可能错过
I'm Ross, by the way.
我是罗斯
Hello,Ross.
罗斯你好
-I love what you've done with this space. -Thank you so much.
我喜欢你家的布置 谢谢你
How hot is this?!
好火辣呀
I'm sorry you're here with me instead of Roger.
可惜在这里的是你不是罗杰
Yeah,me too.
就是啊
Well,I could make it seem like he's here.
我可以让你感到他的存在
"Here's some little-known facts about couscous:
关于库司库司的小常识
They didn't add the second 'cous' until 1979."
第二个库司 是1979年才加的
Stop it! That's not funny!
别闹了，一点也不好笑
I'm sorry,okay? It's just...
好 对不起
tonight was supposed to be a big deal.
今晚原本应该很重要的
-What was tonight? -You don't want to know.
今晚要干嘛？ 你不会想知道
好吧
What was tonight?
今晚要干嘛？
Tonight was going to be my first time.
今晚本来是我的初夜
With Roger?
跟罗杰？
Not just with Roger?
不只是跟罗杰？
Oh,my God.
我的天哪
All right,relax, Mr. I've-Had-Sex-Four-Times!
别激动，只做过四次的先生
Four different women!
是四个不同的女人
I've had sex way more times.
次数就多太多了
-How many? -Nine.
几次？ 九次
I'm just waiting for the perfect guy.
我只是在等完美的对象
Good for you. You really think that Roger's the perfect guy?
这样很好啊 你真的觉得罗杰是那个人？
No, but he's not a horrible guy.
不是，但他也不算糟
That's what I tell girls about me.
我都那样自我介绍
Chandler,I'm gonna die a virgin!
钱德，我会死于处女之身
No,you are not. You are sweet and wonderful...
你不会，你很好很棒
and this is gonna happen for you.
你一定会得到经验
Oh,really? When? Do you want to do it with me?
是吗？什么时候？你想跟我做吗？
Okay.
好啊
I was kidding.
我是开玩笑的
So was I.
我也是
You're such an amazing actor.
乔伊，你真是个了不起的演员
How do you know where Dr. Drake Ramoray leaves off...
你怎么分辨拉莫瑞医生
and Joey Tribbiani begins?
跟乔伊崔比亚尼的转换？
Well,with Dr. Drake...
拉莫瑞医生...
they always tell me what to say.
有现成的台词
And with Joey,I pretty much have to make it up on my own.
乔伊就得自己掰了
Tell me something,Joey.
你告诉我…
-I just fell right off the couch there. -Yeah,you did.
我刚刚从沙发上摔下来 没错
Here you go. Let me ask you a question.
我没事 坐好，我问你一件事
When was the last time...
有多久...
someone told you just how beautiful you are?
没有人称赞你美丽了？
Wow.
I can't feel my hands.
我的手麻了
Come on. Come here.
手给我
We can't do this.
我们不能这么做 没错
Oyster?
吃生蚝？ 好
If we did do this, there'd be a lot of pressure on me.
要是我们做了，我压力会很大
Because you've waited a long time, and I wouldn't want to disappoint you.
因为你等了很久 我不想让你失望
But I have nothing to compare it to.
但是我没得比较
Even if you were horrible, how would I know?
就算你很逊，我哪会知道？
I do like that.
这个好耶
It's harder for me. I have four women to compete with.
我还比较累 我得跟另外四个女人比
Well,if it helps, there were only three.
其实只有三个
So it'd just be for tonight, right?
所以只有今晚对吧？
Absolutely. It would just be one friend helping out another friend.
没错，只是朋友在帮朋友的忙
Stop it. We're not doing this.
别说了，不行
-Let's do it! -No!
来做吧 不行…
Okay!
好吧
Do you have any moves?
你有特定的撇步吗？
I have some moves.
我有一些啦
I have no moves.
我没有
Okay,what you doing there?
你在干什么？
-I'm sorry,this is just too weird. -Yeah,forget it.
对不起，真的太奇怪了 是啊，还是算了
What if I turn out the lights?
要是我关灯呢？ 好
赞
钱德？ 怎样？
That's the couch.
那是沙发
I know.
我知道
Oh,my God!
天哪
I know!
就是啊
I'll tell you something.
告诉你
We are gonna do that again!
我们一定要再来一次
没问题
Morning.
早安
Oh,right.
对喔 没错
Oh,God.
天哪
Oh,I can't believe Joey Tribbiani heard me throw up.
居然让乔伊崔比亚尼 听到我吐
He actually saw you a little bit too.
其实他也看到了一点 不会吧
Oh,God,we didn't...?
天哪，我们没有…没有…
Not after seeing that.
没有，看完就没兴致了
God,I'm just a horrible person.
我真是很糟糕
-Wh..? Why? -Because I'm married.
为什么？ 因为我已经结婚了
That's right,I'm a married woman.
没错，我是有夫之妇
I came to a TV star's apartment to have an affair.
还跑到一个电视明星家搞外遇
That's ridiculous.
别傻了
I'm not a "star."
我才不是明星
I'm just a regular famous actor.
只是一般的名演员
And I'm a horrible,horrible person.
而我是个很糟糕的人
Rachel,will you stop saying that?
瑞秋，你别再自责了
Hey,look.
Remember on the show when Capri was dying?
你记不记得卡普丽丝临死前
-And she gave me.. -The ring from the cave.
给了我… 石洞里的戒指 记得
好…
Oh,my God! They let you keep that stuff?
天哪，你可以留着它？
Sure. As long as they don't find out, you can keep whatever you want.
当然，只要不被发现 想留什么都行
And I want you to have it.
我要把它送给你
No,I couldn't.
不要… 要
Every time you look at it...
你每次看到它
I want you to remember that you are a good person.
就要想起你是个好人
Now,you had the chance to cheat...
你有机会外遇
and with me.
而且还是跟我
But you didn't. And that's what this ring stands for.
但是你没有 这就是这枚戒指的意义
But I thought that ring stood for Capri's undying love for her brother.
我以为它是代表 卡普丽丝对哥哥永不止息的爱
Look,you want the ring or not?
你到底要不要？ 我要
Hey,look at you! You're up!
你醒了 太好了
I thought I'd try to take a walk.
我想去走一走
Will you pour me some water? I'll be back soon.
你们帮我倒杯水，我马上回来
You're not gonna use the pay phone to call work, are you?
你不是想打公共电话回公司吧
No. I've learned my lesson.
不是，我已经学到教训了
Let's go! Come on! Move it!
快点，动作快
Phoebe,come on!
Shoes,briefcase. Thanks,Lou. Good luck with the gallbladder.
鞋子，公事包 谢了，祝你的胆囊早日康复
Hey,Joe...
乔伊
did you ever have a threesome?
你…你玩过3P吗？
Look,Ross,I think Carol's great, and I'm sure you're very attractive,but...
罗斯，我觉得卡萝很漂亮 我也相信你很有魅力，但是…
No. The reason I'm asking is that...
不是，我之所以问你是因为…
I sort of had one last night.
我昨晚玩了3P
You?
你？ 对
All right. So? Was it amazing?
漂亮，过瘾吗？
It was...
还…
okay.
好啦
Just okay? Did you do it right?
只有还好？你的玩法对吗？
Look, it's just, did you ever go to a party and think:
你有没有在参加派对时觉得
"Would anyone really miss me if I weren't here?"
“少了我会有什么差别吗”？
But still,Ross...
不过...
your worst day with two women, pretty much better than any other day.
跟两个女人玩得再难玩 也胜过其他日子
It's just...
只是...
my part seemed to be over pretty quickly...
我这个部分很快就结束了
and then there was a lot of waiting around.
然后我就一直等
But you got to be with both of them.
你两个都有做到吧？
Not really.
没有
Just Carol.
我只有跟卡萝做
-Not the other one? -No,she kept kicking me away.
另一个没有？ 没有，她一直把我踹开
You don't want that.
那样很讨厌 就是啊
At least you got to see a lot of stuff.
至少你开了眼界
Oh,I saw a lot of stuff.
是大大的开了眼界
-You get a little bored? -A little.
你后来有点无聊？ 有一点
Made a snack.
我弄了点吃的
-What'd you have? -Just a sandwich.
你弄了什么？ 就是三明治
Turkey. A little mustard.
火鸡肉，加一点芥末酱
-Sounds good. -It really was.
好像很赞 是很赞
Let me tell you about this chick I scored with last night.
我昨晚跟一个女生全垒打
Wait a minute,that was you.
等等，就是你嘛
Hey,check me out. I'm a slut!
你看我，我是个贱人
So you want to do something tonight?
晚上要不要找事情做？
I can't. Dr. Roger's coming over again.
不行，罗杰医生又要来了
Oh,right.
也对
Because you're still seeing him, and he's a good guy.
因为你还在跟他交往 他人很好
I remember a time....
我记得有一次…
Are you okay?
你还好吧？
Yeah,totally.
好得很…你呢？
Totally. Are you?
棒呆了
Great. It's so amazing.
真的好神奇
Last time Dr. Roger came over, I was so nervous.
上次罗杰来的时候我好紧张
But after being with you, I'm like,"Can the doctor see me now?"
但是跟你做过之后，我变成 “医生可以看我了吗？”
I bet he can.
一定可以
"l don't have an appointment, but I sure could use a physical."
我没有预约，但是我需要体检
-You sure you're okay? -Don't worry about me,I'll be fine.
你真的没事？ 没事，别管我，我很好
My God! Barry!
天哪，贝瑞
You said you were going to be away all weekend!
你说你周末都不在
That's right! I'm sorry! I am early!
没错，对不起，我回来早了
Finish, please!
你们请继续
Surprise! Look who's back!
惊喜！看看谁回来了
菲比
Call security.
通知警卫
Phoebe,didn't you get fired?
菲比，你不是被开除了吗？
I don't think so.
我可不这么认为
菲比？ 杰克
-What are you doing here? -All better. Back to work.
你来干什么？ 我好多了，回来上班
This clown from research told me I was fired.
但这个研究部猪头说我被开除
He should do his research,huh?
他应该用功一点
Well,you were fired.
你是被开除了
没有
I told that guy who answered your phone.
我跟帮你接电话的人说了
I didn't get that message. So this doesn't count.
我没收到留言，所以不算
Anyway,I'll be in my office.
我先进办公室了
Phoebe,you don't have an office.
菲比，没有你的办公室
I'll work right here.
没关系，我在这里工作
This is good. Next to this plant.
这里很好，旁边有植物
You're in my office.
菲比 你闯入我的办公室了
I've made a lot of cash for this company. I am talking big bucks!
我替这家公司赚了很多钱 而且是大钱
Pesos! Yen! Rubles! You make one little mistake..
披索、日圆、卢布 我才犯了一个小错…
You lost 13 million dollars.
你损失了1千3百万美元
So now this is all about money?
原来一切都是为了钱
You know, it's bad enough that...
我已经够…
You have got to be kidding.
别闹了吧
-Are you all right? -I'm having another heart attack.
你还好吗？我又发作了 什么？
I'm having another heart attack!
我的心脏病又发作了
Call 911!
叫救护车
Dumb-ass!
猪头
Phoebe,how's it going?
菲比，你好吗？
They fired me, and I'm having a heart attack.
我被开除，心脏病发作
Well,welcome back.
欢迎归队
Is Joey Tribbiani here?
乔伊崔比亚尼在吗？ 不在
If you see him,please tell him I'm looking for him...
如果你见到他 请转告他我在找他
and that this time I am not gonna throw up!
这次我不会吐了
Well,that's always good news.
这永远是件好事
Are you okay?
你还好吗？
Me? I'm great!
我？我很好
I'm fine! I'm so good!
我很好，我好得不得了
But you know who's not great?
但是你知道谁不好？
Men!
男人
You're a man, right, Ross?
你是男人对吧？ 对
Sit down.
坐下 好
Let me ask you something.
我问你一件事
Do wedding vows mean squat to you people?
婚誓对你们来说是个屁吗？
Why is it that the second we tell you we are going out of town...
为什么我们一说要出门
bam, there you are in bed with the neighbor's dog-walker?
砰！你们就跟邻居的 遛狗小妹上床？
We're sorry.
我们很抱歉
No,seriously. Seriously. What has happened to the sanctity of marriage?
我说真的，婚姻的神圣性呢？
-Didn't you spend last night at Joey's? -What are you,a detective?
你昨晚不是跟乔伊在一起？ 你是侦探吗？
I don't know what's going on with you and your husband...
我不知道你和你丈夫怎么了…
and what is hopefully an adult dog-walker.
希望那位遛狗妹已经成年
Look,can I just say, not all men are like that.
但我要说男人并非都那样
There are men who'll do anything to make their marriage work.
有些男人愿意尽全力挽回婚姻
Men who will stand by and watch...
有些男人愿意退到一边
as their wives engage in what can only be described as a "twosome"...
看老婆跟健身房刚认识的女人
with some woman she barely knows from the gym!
打得火热旁若无人
Who are these men?
这些男人是谁？
Just men. A guy I know.
就是我认识的一个人
Well,you might want to tell him it sounds like his wife...
你可能要告诉他 听起来他的老婆...
is gay.
是同性恋
She is not...
她才不是…
She's gay.
她是同性恋
Oh,my God.
天哪
She is so gay!
她好同性恋
I can't believe this.
我真不敢相信
Good day for married people,huh?
已婚者的黄道吉日
I'm sorry your husband cheated on you.
很遗撼你老公不忠
I'm sorry your wife is gay.
很遗撼你老婆是同性恋
I guess women aren't that great either.
看来女人也没那么好
Try telling my wife that.
去告诉我老婆啊
Okay to come in?
我可以进来吗？
Come in, eat, whatever you want.
进来，吃饭，随你便
Dr. Roger got beeped again.
罗杰医生又被叫走了
Yeah,I know. Guess who beeped him.
我知道，你猜是谁找他？
I'm the ruptured spleen.
我就是那个脾脏破裂病患
Why would you do that?
你为什么要这样？
Because you shouldn't be with him.
因为你不该和他在一起
You should be with me.
你应该和我在一起
Really?
是吗？
When you were talking about Roger, that was killing me.
听你聊罗杰让我好痛苦
Things like last night, they don't just happen.
昨晚的事不是说有就有的
At least not to me. I mean, with the other two women...
至少对我来说不是 跟另外两个女人在一起时…
in the morning, I couldn't wait to go hang out with my friends.
到了早上 我巴不得赶快去找朋友
But with you...
但是跟你…
I was,you know, already with a friend.
我就是跟朋友在一起
You probably don't want to go out with me.
你八成不想跟我交往
I make too many jokes, I've never been in a serious relationship...
因为我太爱开玩笑 也没认真谈过感情
and I'm not technically a "doctor."
又不是个“医生”
There was just one woman, wasn't there?
只有一个女人对不对？
No, there were two.
真的有两个
-Including me? -Oh,yeah.
一个是我？ 正是
It only takes two heart attacks To finally make you see
两次心脏病发才终于让你认清
One of them won't do it But the second will set you free
一次死不了 但第二次会让你解脱
Tell all your hate and anger It's time to say goodbye
告诉你的恨意与愤怒 是该道别了
And that is just what I will do
那正是我要做的
Soon as those bastards I worked for Die
只要我的老板们一死